Fungi play an important role in ecosystems, are a source of food, and make key contributions to the world of medicine.
真菌在生态系统中扮演着重要角色，是食物的来源，并且对医学界做出关键贡献。
So, why do we know so little about them?
那么，为什么我们对它们知之甚少呢？
An estimated two million fungal species – more than 90% of all fungi – have yet to be described by science, according to Rebecca Morelle, science reporter for the BBC.
据BBC科学记者丽贝卡·莫雷尔称，估计有200万种真菌——占所有真菌的90%以上——尚未被科学描述。
In the UK alone, there are thought to be around 25,000 species of fungi – five or six times more than plants.
仅在英国，就有大约25,000种真菌，是植物种类的五六倍。
Scientists are trying to find out more about this largely unexplored world, but it is challenging.
科学家们正试图进一步探索这个很大程度上未经探索的世界，但这颇具挑战性。
Dr Martyn Ainsworth, a senior researcher from Royal Botanic Gardens, Kew, in London, says: 'We can grow a certain number in the lab, but there is a whole host of fungi that we cannot grow in the lab.
伦敦皇家邱园的高级研究员马丁·安斯沃思博士说："我们可以在实验室中培养一定数量的真菌，但还有大量真菌我们无法在实验室中培养。
This has held back a lot of research.'
这阻碍了许多研究。"
The fact that we know so little about the world of fungi leads many of us to misunderstand them.
我们对真菌世界知之甚少这一事实导致许多人误解它们。"
'A lot of people are afraid of poisonous mushrooms', says Dr Jassy Drakulic, a plant pathologist, 'but only a very small proportion of the thousands of species of fungi in the world can cause disease'.
很多人都害怕毒蘑菇，"植物病理学家贾西·德拉库利奇博士说，"但世界上数千种真菌中，只有极少数能引起疾病。"
Most are harmless and often beneficial, called by some 'the hidden helpers of our environment'.
大多数真菌是无害且常常是有益的，被一些人称为"环境中隐藏的帮手"。
Some fungi provide food and shelter for wildlife, help plants absorb water and nutrients and recycle waste and dead matter.
一些真菌为野生动物提供食物和庇护所，帮助植物吸收水分和养分，并循环利用废物和无机物。
Other types of fungi grow on the roots of trees and plants, forming a huge underground network that helps nourish trees.
其他类型的真菌生长在树木和植物的根部，形成一个巨大的地下网络，帮助滋养树木。
'Fungi are really the behind-the-scenes team that are doing all the work', adds Dr Ainsworth.
安斯沃思博士补充说："真菌实际上是幕后做所有工作的团队。"
So, next time you add mushrooms to your dinner, take a painkiller for a headache, or go for a walk through the woods, remember to thank the living things that made it all possible – fungi.
所以，下次你在晚餐中加入蘑菇，服用止痛药缓解头痛，或者去树林里散步时，记得感谢让这一切成为可能的生物——真菌。